{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868372586","data":{"timestamp":" 946868372586"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mwalimu-kabisa-bwana-msituni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868375648","data":{"timestamp":" 946868375648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mwalimu-kabisa-bwana-msituni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" kabisa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868378400","data":{"timestamp":" 946868378400"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mwalimu-kabisa-bwana-msituni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" bwana"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868381411","data":{"timestamp":" 946868381411"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mwalimu-kabisa-bwana-msituni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868405646","data":{"timestamp":" 946868405646"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_msituni-bwana-vizuri-mrembo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868449500","data":{"timestamp":" 946868449500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jitu_kabla-furaha-jitu-vizuri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jitu"," userResponse":" kabla"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868452898","data":{"timestamp":" 946868452898"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jitu_kabla-furaha-jitu-vizuri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jitu"," userResponse":" furaha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868456481","data":{"timestamp":" 946868456481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jitu_kabla-furaha-jitu-vizuri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jitu"," userResponse":" jitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868475232","data":{"timestamp":" 946868475231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msitu_msitu-wako-sokoni-mjomba"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msitu"," userResponse":" msitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868510382","data":{"timestamp":" 946868510381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_uchungu-msituni-mtu-hakuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868519935","data":{"timestamp":" 946868519933"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" msituni_uchungu-msituni-mtu-hakuna"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868520052","data":{"timestamp":" 946868520052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 9eb11d1c-9354-4cf0-bbe7-9611d54a88a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868556357","data":{"timestamp":" 946868556357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ardhi-ndiyo-mlima-mjomba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" ardhi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868561973","data":{"timestamp":" 946868561973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ardhi-ndiyo-mlima-mjomba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" ndiyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868567253","data":{"timestamp":" 946868567253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ardhi-ndiyo-mlima-mjomba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868606105","data":{"timestamp":" 946868606105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_tamu-tofauti-kuna-kasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868632006","data":{"timestamp":" 946868632006"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_barabara-au-kuna-gani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" barabara"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868659039","data":{"timestamp":" 946868659038"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_gari-simu-mkono-kule"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868695258","data":{"timestamp":" 946868695257"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gari_gari-simu-mkono-kule"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868695375","data":{"timestamp":" 946868695375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 7b567e27-bd2f-48cd-b31a-198ea183ddee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868715890","data":{"timestamp":" 946868715890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868720261","data":{"timestamp":" 946868720260"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868723816","data":{"timestamp":" 946868723815"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868731531","data":{"timestamp":" 946868731531"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868738481","data":{"timestamp":" 946868738480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868744237","data":{"timestamp":" 946868744236"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" ede30b96-3e6a-4e64-9e8f-75060dd8ba15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868786187","data":{"timestamp":" 946868786187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-7-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868795760","data":{"timestamp":" 946868795759"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-5-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868805291","data":{"timestamp":" 946868805291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-1-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868812861","data":{"timestamp":" 946868812861"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868818282","data":{"timestamp":" 946868818282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-3-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868842720","data":{"timestamp":" 946868842720"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868847612","data":{"timestamp":" 946868847612"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868857566","data":{"timestamp":" 946868857566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868900887","data":{"timestamp":" 946868900887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_7-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868906015","data":{"timestamp":" 946868906015"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-7-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868911538","data":{"timestamp":" 946868911538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-0-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868918276","data":{"timestamp":" 946868918274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" b44ab887-64f4-4763-a7cc-bb6c1d0aaafb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-0-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868931337","data":{"timestamp":" 946868931337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-d-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868935362","data":{"timestamp":" 946868935362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868939622","data":{"timestamp":" 946868939622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-w-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868944169","data":{"timestamp":" 946868944169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868948169","data":{"timestamp":" 946868948169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868953914","data":{"timestamp":" 946868953913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" c42cd2d0-4387-48c4-b2b6-2701e7b63ca4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868964495","data":{"timestamp":" 946868964495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868965014","data":{"timestamp":" 946868965013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868966175","data":{"timestamp":" 946868966174"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868969014","data":{"timestamp":" 946868969014"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868969736","data":{"timestamp":" 946868969736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868970320","data":{"timestamp":" 946868970320"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868973205","data":{"timestamp":" 946868973204"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868973907","data":{"timestamp":" 946868973907"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868974427","data":{"timestamp":" 946868974427"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868974637","data":{"timestamp":" 946868974636"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868975500","data":{"timestamp":" 946868975499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868978214","data":{"timestamp":" 946868978213"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868978757","data":{"timestamp":" 946868978756"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868979810","data":{"timestamp":" 946868979809"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868982595","data":{"timestamp":" 946868982595"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868983325","data":{"timestamp":" 946868983325"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868983907","data":{"timestamp":" 946868983906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868986797","data":{"timestamp":" 946868986796"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868987507","data":{"timestamp":" 946868987507"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868987998","data":{"timestamp":" 946868987998"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868988211","data":{"timestamp":" 946868988210"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868988903","data":{"timestamp":" 946868988903"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868992200","data":{"timestamp":" 946868992200"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868992805","data":{"timestamp":" 946868992805"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868994463","data":{"timestamp":" 946868994463"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" ALIPALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868995270","data":{"timestamp":" 946868995270"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868995814","data":{"timestamp":" 946868995813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868996439","data":{"timestamp":" 946868996438"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868999297","data":{"timestamp":" 946868999297"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946868999781","data":{"timestamp":" 946868999780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869001494","data":{"timestamp":" 946869001494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869002258","data":{"timestamp":" 946869002258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869002803","data":{"timestamp":" 946869002802"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869003378","data":{"timestamp":" 946869003378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869006379","data":{"timestamp":" 946869006378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869006649","data":{"timestamp":" 946869006648"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869007372","data":{"timestamp":" 946869007372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869008196","data":{"timestamp":" 946869008196"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869008899","data":{"timestamp":" 946869008899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869009479","data":{"timestamp":" 946869009479"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869010223","data":{"timestamp":" 946869010222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869010993","data":{"timestamp":" 946869010993"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869011472","data":{"timestamp":" 946869011472"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZO"," userResponse":" HIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869012012","data":{"timestamp":" 946869012011"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869014397","data":{"timestamp":" 946869014397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869014696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869014696"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869015246","data":{"timestamp":" 946869015246"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869016208","data":{"timestamp":" 946869016207"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869016780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869016780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVUNA"," userResponse":" TULIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869017503","data":{"timestamp":" 946869017502"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869017825","data":{"timestamp":" 946869017825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869018715","data":{"timestamp":" 946869018715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869021988","data":{"timestamp":" 946869021987"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869022507","data":{"timestamp":" 946869022507"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869022743","data":{"timestamp":" 946869022743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869023643","data":{"timestamp":" 946869023642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869024593","data":{"timestamp":" 946869024593"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869025589","data":{"timestamp":" 946869025588"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869025804","data":{"timestamp":" 946869025804"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869026680","data":{"timestamp":" 946869026679"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869029279","data":{"timestamp":" 946869029279"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869029788","data":{"timestamp":" 946869029788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869029991","data":{"timestamp":" 946869029991"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869030672","data":{"timestamp":" 946869030671"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869031698","data":{"timestamp":" 946869031698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869032684","data":{"timestamp":" 946869032684"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869032960","data":{"timestamp":" 946869032960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869033660","data":{"timestamp":" 946869033659"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869036438","data":{"timestamp":" 946869036438"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869036953","data":{"timestamp":" 946869036952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869038105","data":{"timestamp":" 946869038104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869041063","data":{"timestamp":" 946869041062"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869041795","data":{"timestamp":" 946869041795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869042435","data":{"timestamp":" 946869042435"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869044986","data":{"timestamp":" 946869044986"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869045593","data":{"timestamp":" 946869045593"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869046884","data":{"timestamp":" 946869046883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869047744","data":{"timestamp":" 946869047743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869047990","data":{"timestamp":" 946869047989"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869048860","data":{"timestamp":" 946869048860"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869051768","data":{"timestamp":" 946869051768"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869052309","data":{"timestamp":" 946869052308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869053367","data":{"timestamp":" 946869053366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869056229","data":{"timestamp":" 946869056228"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869056961","data":{"timestamp":" 946869056961"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869057606","data":{"timestamp":" 946869057606"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869060165","data":{"timestamp":" 946869060165"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869060742","data":{"timestamp":" 946869060741"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869061975","data":{"timestamp":" 946869061973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869062818","data":{"timestamp":" 946869062818"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869063066","data":{"timestamp":" 946869063065"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869063779","data":{"timestamp":" 946869063779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869066501","data":{"timestamp":" 946869066500"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869066607","data":{"timestamp":" 946869066607"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8f742d25-3c95-41f8-8575-ec68d1a59313"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869075810","data":{"timestamp":" 946869075810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869079575","data":{"timestamp":" 946869079575"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869083272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869083272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869086978","data":{"timestamp":" 946869086978"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-a-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869090743","data":{"timestamp":" 946869090743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869094213","data":{"timestamp":" 946869094213"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-o-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869097827","data":{"timestamp":" 946869097827"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-u"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869101214","data":{"timestamp":" 946869101214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869104786","data":{"timestamp":" 946869104786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869109477","data":{"timestamp":" 946869109477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-e-o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869115223","data":{"timestamp":" 946869115222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8454cf95-9d29-4fb6-b61d-65e08a1a313e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-e-o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869134900","data":{"timestamp":" 946869134900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869141588","data":{"timestamp":" 946869141587"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869148229","data":{"timestamp":" 946869148229"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869154887","data":{"timestamp":" 946869154886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869161533","data":{"timestamp":" 946869161533"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869168183","data":{"timestamp":" 946869168183"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869174852","data":{"timestamp":" 946869174852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869181494","data":{"timestamp":" 946869181494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_2_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869188133","data":{"timestamp":" 946869188133"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869194834","data":{"timestamp":" 946869194834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869208004","data":{"timestamp":" 946869208003"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" aeb960b0-08a9-47c4-b3da-f6a8c3002bd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_7_4_0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869219232","data":{"timestamp":" 946869219232"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869219982","data":{"timestamp":" 946869219982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869220815","data":{"timestamp":" 946869220814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869221696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869221696"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869222293","data":{"timestamp":" 946869222293"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869223045","data":{"timestamp":" 946869223045"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869225493","data":{"timestamp":" 946869225492"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869226014","data":{"timestamp":" 946869226014"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869226875","data":{"timestamp":" 946869226874"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869227835","data":{"timestamp":" 946869227835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869228388","data":{"timestamp":" 946869228387"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869229106","data":{"timestamp":" 946869229106"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869231975","data":{"timestamp":" 946869231974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869232698","data":{"timestamp":" 946869232697"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869232811","data":{"timestamp":" 946869232811"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234233","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234233"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234623","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869234665","data":{"timestamp":" 946869234665"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869238380","data":{"timestamp":" 946869238380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869239046","data":{"timestamp":" 946869239045"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869239975","data":{"timestamp":" 946869239974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869240857","data":{"timestamp":" 946869240856"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869241078","data":{"timestamp":" 946869241078"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869241122","data":{"timestamp":" 946869241122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869245403","data":{"timestamp":" 946869245402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246026","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246026"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246112","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246112"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869246894","data":{"timestamp":" 946869246893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869247819","data":{"timestamp":" 946869247819"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869249071","data":{"timestamp":" 946869249069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869251272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869251272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869251980","data":{"timestamp":" 946869251980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869252253","data":{"timestamp":" 946869252253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869253335","data":{"timestamp":" 946869253335"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869253889","data":{"timestamp":" 946869253889"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869253937","data":{"timestamp":" 946869253937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869258376","data":{"timestamp":" 946869258376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869258983","data":{"timestamp":" 946869258983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869259806","data":{"timestamp":" 946869259806"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869259942","data":{"timestamp":" 946869259942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869260696","data":{"timestamp":" 946869260695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869262027","data":{"timestamp":" 946869262026"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869264433","data":{"timestamp":" 946869264432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869264931","data":{"timestamp":" 946869264931"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869265947","data":{"timestamp":" 946869265945"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869266822","data":{"timestamp":" 946869266822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869267424","data":{"timestamp":" 946869267423"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869268225","data":{"timestamp":" 946869268225"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869271379","data":{"timestamp":" 946869271378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869273352","data":{"timestamp":" 946869273351"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869273601","data":{"timestamp":" 946869273601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869273992","data":{"timestamp":" 946869273991"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869274200","data":{"timestamp":" 946869274199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869275093","data":{"timestamp":" 946869275092"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869277948","data":{"timestamp":" 946869277947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869278419","data":{"timestamp":" 946869278418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869279422","data":{"timestamp":" 946869279422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869279614","data":{"timestamp":" 946869279614"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869280878","data":{"timestamp":" 946869280878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869281697","data":{"timestamp":" 946869281697"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869284349","data":{"timestamp":" 946869284347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869284448","data":{"timestamp":" 946869284448"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 572d644d-31d4-4c54-bd32-1b0b42cac61e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869295034","data":{"timestamp":" 946869295033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869295631","data":{"timestamp":" 946869295630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869296722","data":{"timestamp":" 946869296719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869297719","data":{"timestamp":" 946869297719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869297906","data":{"timestamp":" 946869297906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869298357","data":{"timestamp":" 946869298357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869299109","data":{"timestamp":" 946869299108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869300063","data":{"timestamp":" 946869300063"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869302436","data":{"timestamp":" 946869302435"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869303093","data":{"timestamp":" 946869303093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869304273","data":{"timestamp":" 946869304273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869305221","data":{"timestamp":" 946869305220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869305989","data":{"timestamp":" 946869305988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869306796","data":{"timestamp":" 946869306795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" WAPENZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869307610","data":{"timestamp":" 946869307610"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869310466","data":{"timestamp":" 946869310466"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869311540","data":{"timestamp":" 946869311540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869312179","data":{"timestamp":" 946869312179"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869312961","data":{"timestamp":" 946869312961"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869313494","data":{"timestamp":" 946869313493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869313878","data":{"timestamp":" 946869313878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869314411","data":{"timestamp":" 946869314411"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869314802","data":{"timestamp":" 946869314801"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869316321","data":{"timestamp":" 946869316321"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" ILIMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869316855","data":{"timestamp":" 946869316854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869317781","data":{"timestamp":" 946869317780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869321067","data":{"timestamp":" 946869321066"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869322282","data":{"timestamp":" 946869322282"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869322985","data":{"timestamp":" 946869322984"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869323477","data":{"timestamp":" 946869323476"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869324371","data":{"timestamp":" 946869324371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" UKAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869324893","data":{"timestamp":" 946869324893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869325790","data":{"timestamp":" 946869325789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869328135","data":{"timestamp":" 946869328134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869329418","data":{"timestamp":" 946869329418"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" NIANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869330310","data":{"timestamp":" 946869330310"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869330794","data":{"timestamp":" 946869330794"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869331491","data":{"timestamp":" 946869331491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869331906","data":{"timestamp":" 946869331906"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869334913","data":{"timestamp":" 946869334913"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869335404","data":{"timestamp":" 946869335403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869336161","data":{"timestamp":" 946869336161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869336961","data":{"timestamp":" 946869336961"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869337538","data":{"timestamp":" 946869337537"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869338341","data":{"timestamp":" 946869338341"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869341317","data":{"timestamp":" 946869341317"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869342202","data":{"timestamp":" 946869342202"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869343694","data":{"timestamp":" 946869343694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" SIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869346063","data":{"timestamp":" 946869346062"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869346703","data":{"timestamp":" 946869346703"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869347761","data":{"timestamp":" 946869347758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869348570","data":{"timestamp":" 946869348567"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869349455","data":{"timestamp":" 946869349454"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" UKIWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869350192","data":{"timestamp":" 946869350191"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" MEKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869353055","data":{"timestamp":" 946869353054"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869353108","data":{"timestamp":" 946869353108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869356780","data":{"timestamp":" 946869356780"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869357190","data":{"timestamp":" 946869357190"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869357822","data":{"timestamp":" 946869357822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869358630","data":{"timestamp":" 946869358630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869359355","data":{"timestamp":" 946869359354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869360195","data":{"timestamp":" 946869360194"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869362538","data":{"timestamp":" 946869362535"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" FYATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869363380","data":{"timestamp":" 946869363379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" ULIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869363893","data":{"timestamp":" 946869363893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869364250","data":{"timestamp":" 946869364249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869366781","data":{"timestamp":" 946869366781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869368302","data":{"timestamp":" 946869368301"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869371417","data":{"timestamp":" 946869371416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869372033","data":{"timestamp":" 946869372032"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869372806","data":{"timestamp":" 946869372805"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869373645","data":{"timestamp":" 946869373645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869374009","data":{"timestamp":" 946869374007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869374631","data":{"timestamp":" 946869374630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" KUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869375106","data":{"timestamp":" 946869375105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869375918","data":{"timestamp":" 946869375918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869379179","data":{"timestamp":" 946869379178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869380059","data":{"timestamp":" 946869380057"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" YALIPOANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869380963","data":{"timestamp":" 946869380962"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" KUCHEMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869382961","data":{"timestamp":" 946869382959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869383468","data":{"timestamp":" 946869383468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869386069","data":{"timestamp":" 946869386069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869386675","data":{"timestamp":" 946869386674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869387044","data":{"timestamp":" 946869387044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869388218","data":{"timestamp":" 946869388218"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" IKACHOMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869388683","data":{"timestamp":" 946869388682"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869389207","data":{"timestamp":" 946869389206"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869389642","data":{"timestamp":" 946869389641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869390685","data":{"timestamp":" 946869390683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" UKAKATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869393336","data":{"timestamp":" 946869393335"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869393939","data":{"timestamp":" 946869393938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" BADALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869394138","data":{"timestamp":" 946869394138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869395180","data":{"timestamp":" 946869395179"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" KUMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869395380","data":{"timestamp":" 946869395380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869395775","data":{"timestamp":" 946869395774"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869396417","data":{"timestamp":" 946869396417"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869396833","data":{"timestamp":" 946869396832"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869397510","data":{"timestamp":" 946869397509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869398770","data":{"timestamp":" 946869398770"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869399035","data":{"timestamp":" 946869399034"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869399639","data":{"timestamp":" 946869399638"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869400480","data":{"timestamp":" 946869400480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869401143","data":{"timestamp":" 946869401142"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869403622","data":{"timestamp":" 946869403621"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869403719","data":{"timestamp":" 946869403719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5ca37537-491b-42d3-9d32-eee133c6baa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869413254","data":{"timestamp":" 946869413254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869416481","data":{"timestamp":" 946869416481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869419852","data":{"timestamp":" 946869419852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869423181","data":{"timestamp":" 946869423180"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869426844","data":{"timestamp":" 946869426844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869430671","data":{"timestamp":" 946869430671"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_a-i-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869434428","data":{"timestamp":" 946869434428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_i-u-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869437707","data":{"timestamp":" 946869437707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-u-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869441027","data":{"timestamp":" 946869441027"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869444188","data":{"timestamp":" 946869444187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869449939","data":{"timestamp":" 946869449938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5a540323-6135-4fe6-8fe4-abd31e79e218"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869459963","data":{"timestamp":" 946869459963"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-1-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869465508","data":{"timestamp":" 946869465508"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-3-8"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869470901","data":{"timestamp":" 946869470901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869475765","data":{"timestamp":" 946869475765"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-5-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869480670","data":{"timestamp":" 946869480669"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869486223","data":{"timestamp":" 946869486223"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_5-3-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869491475","data":{"timestamp":" 946869491475"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-0-8"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869496709","data":{"timestamp":" 946869496708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869501783","data":{"timestamp":" 946869501782"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-3-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869506831","data":{"timestamp":" 946869506831"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869513571","data":{"timestamp":" 946869513571"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bb9f3502-244c-4c3c-a756-1a75d1795b58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-0-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869534656","data":{"timestamp":" 946869534656"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_o_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869541288","data":{"timestamp":" 946869541288"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_i_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869547943","data":{"timestamp":" 946869547943"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_o_a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869554600","data":{"timestamp":" 946869554600"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869561249","data":{"timestamp":" 946869561249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_u_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869567903","data":{"timestamp":" 946869567903"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869574547","data":{"timestamp":" 946869574546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869581217","data":{"timestamp":" 946869581217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_i_u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869587900","data":{"timestamp":" 946869587900"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_i_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869594542","data":{"timestamp":" 946869594541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_u_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869607626","data":{"timestamp":" 946869607626"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" cc57f4de-6fbf-425c-aed3-2811b15f4ae8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_O..O.vow.10.rand.say.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_a_u_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869617685","data":{"timestamp":" 946869617685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869618738","data":{"timestamp":" 946869618737"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869620084","data":{"timestamp":" 946869620084"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869620954","data":{"timestamp":" 946869620954"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869621890","data":{"timestamp":" 946869621890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869622481","data":{"timestamp":" 946869622481"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869623395","data":{"timestamp":" 946869623394"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869626829","data":{"timestamp":" 946869626828"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869627396","data":{"timestamp":" 946869627396"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869628116","data":{"timestamp":" 946869628115"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869628699","data":{"timestamp":" 946869628699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869628878","data":{"timestamp":" 946869628878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869630115","data":{"timestamp":" 946869630112"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869633857","data":{"timestamp":" 946869633857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869634346","data":{"timestamp":" 946869634345"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869635154","data":{"timestamp":" 946869635154"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869636125","data":{"timestamp":" 946869636125"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" ULIOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869639556","data":{"timestamp":" 946869639556"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869640134","data":{"timestamp":" 946869640134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869640849","data":{"timestamp":" 946869640849"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869641440","data":{"timestamp":" 946869641440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869641621","data":{"timestamp":" 946869641620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869642854","data":{"timestamp":" 946869642853"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869646555","data":{"timestamp":" 946869646555"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANATANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869647358","data":{"timestamp":" 946869647357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869648092","data":{"timestamp":" 946869648092"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869649190","data":{"timestamp":" 946869649189"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869649774","data":{"timestamp":" 946869649773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869653136","data":{"timestamp":" 946869653135"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869653707","data":{"timestamp":" 946869653707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869654428","data":{"timestamp":" 946869654427"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869655015","data":{"timestamp":" 946869655015"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869655191","data":{"timestamp":" 946869655191"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869656426","data":{"timestamp":" 946869656426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869660408","data":{"timestamp":" 946869660408"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869661102","data":{"timestamp":" 946869661102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869661695","data":{"timestamp":" 946869661695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869661946","data":{"timestamp":" 946869661945"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869662969","data":{"timestamp":" 946869662968"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" MABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869663622","data":{"timestamp":" 946869663622"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869667163","data":{"timestamp":" 946869667163"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869667739","data":{"timestamp":" 946869667738"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869668469","data":{"timestamp":" 946869668466"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869669072","data":{"timestamp":" 946869669072"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869669253","data":{"timestamp":" 946869669253"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869670490","data":{"timestamp":" 946869670490"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869673940","data":{"timestamp":" 946869673938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869674403","data":{"timestamp":" 946869674403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869674995","data":{"timestamp":" 946869674994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869675268","data":{"timestamp":" 946869675267"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869676122","data":{"timestamp":" 946869676122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869676276","data":{"timestamp":" 946869676275"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869676964","data":{"timestamp":" 946869676964"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" BLUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869680383","data":{"timestamp":" 946869680383"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869680966","data":{"timestamp":" 946869680965"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869681688","data":{"timestamp":" 946869681688"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869682277","data":{"timestamp":" 946869682276"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869682457","data":{"timestamp":" 946869682456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869683687","data":{"timestamp":" 946869683687"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869687120","data":{"timestamp":" 946869687120"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPIGA"," userResponse":" ANAPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869688002","data":{"timestamp":" 946869688000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869688593","data":{"timestamp":" 946869688592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869689166","data":{"timestamp":" 946869689165"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869689437","data":{"timestamp":" 946869689437"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869690286","data":{"timestamp":" 946869690285"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869690962","data":{"timestamp":" 946869690962"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" AINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869691248","data":{"timestamp":" 946869691247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869692191","data":{"timestamp":" 946869692190"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHANO"," userResponse":" LUGHANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869695604","data":{"timestamp":" 946869695604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869696177","data":{"timestamp":" 946869696177"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869696890","data":{"timestamp":" 946869696890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869697479","data":{"timestamp":" 946869697479"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869697662","data":{"timestamp":" 946869697662"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869698895","data":{"timestamp":" 946869698894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869702273","data":{"timestamp":" 946869702272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869702651","data":{"timestamp":" 946869702650"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869703205","data":{"timestamp":" 946869703199"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869704081","data":{"timestamp":" 946869704080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869707482","data":{"timestamp":" 946869707482"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869708069","data":{"timestamp":" 946869708069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869708787","data":{"timestamp":" 946869708786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869709376","data":{"timestamp":" 946869709375"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869709555","data":{"timestamp":" 946869709555"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869710789","data":{"timestamp":" 946869710789"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869714078","data":{"timestamp":" 946869714078"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869714722","data":{"timestamp":" 946869714722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869714844","data":{"timestamp":" 946869714844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869715326","data":{"timestamp":" 946869715326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869715688","data":{"timestamp":" 946869715688"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869716334","data":{"timestamp":" 946869716333"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869716494","data":{"timestamp":" 946869716494"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869717461","data":{"timestamp":" 946869717460"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" MACHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869720882","data":{"timestamp":" 946869720881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869721458","data":{"timestamp":" 946869721457"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869722173","data":{"timestamp":" 946869722173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869722758","data":{"timestamp":" 946869722758"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869722937","data":{"timestamp":" 946869722936"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869724169","data":{"timestamp":" 946869724169"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869727507","data":{"timestamp":" 946869727506"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869728304","data":{"timestamp":" 946869728304"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869728928","data":{"timestamp":" 946869728928"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869729785","data":{"timestamp":" 946869729784"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEUSI"," userResponse":" VYEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869733325","data":{"timestamp":" 946869733324"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869733897","data":{"timestamp":" 946869733897"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869734612","data":{"timestamp":" 946869734612"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869735195","data":{"timestamp":" 946869735195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869735375","data":{"timestamp":" 946869735374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869736605","data":{"timestamp":" 946869736605"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869739957","data":{"timestamp":" 946869739957"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869740655","data":{"timestamp":" 946869740655"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869741801","data":{"timestamp":" 946869741801"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869745250","data":{"timestamp":" 946869745250"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869745829","data":{"timestamp":" 946869745829"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869746552","data":{"timestamp":" 946869746552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869747138","data":{"timestamp":" 946869747137"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869747313","data":{"timestamp":" 946869747313"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869748554","data":{"timestamp":" 946869748553"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869752294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869752294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" ANAJIFUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869753129","data":{"timestamp":" 946869753128"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869753311","data":{"timestamp":" 946869753311"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869754685","data":{"timestamp":" 946869754684"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAYANSI"," userResponse":" SAYANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869755485","data":{"timestamp":" 946869755484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869756912","data":{"timestamp":" 946869756912"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJAMII"," userResponse":" KIJAMII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869757375","data":{"timestamp":" 946869757374"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869758266","data":{"timestamp":" 946869758266"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HESABU"," userResponse":" HESABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869761595","data":{"timestamp":" 946869761595"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869762173","data":{"timestamp":" 946869762173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869762889","data":{"timestamp":" 946869762888"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869763481","data":{"timestamp":" 946869763480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869763667","data":{"timestamp":" 946869763666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869764897","data":{"timestamp":" 946869764897"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869768328","data":{"timestamp":" 946869768328"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869768598","data":{"timestamp":" 946869768598"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869769499","data":{"timestamp":" 946869769499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869771634","data":{"timestamp":" 946869771634"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," userResponse":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869772867","data":{"timestamp":" 946869772866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869773159","data":{"timestamp":" 946869773159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869773791","data":{"timestamp":" 946869773790"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869774014","data":{"timestamp":" 946869774013"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869774654","data":{"timestamp":" 946869774654"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869777997","data":{"timestamp":" 946869777997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869778571","data":{"timestamp":" 946869778570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869779285","data":{"timestamp":" 946869779284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869779876","data":{"timestamp":" 946869779876"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869780054","data":{"timestamp":" 946869780054"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869781278","data":{"timestamp":" 946869781277"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869783942","data":{"timestamp":" 946869783940"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869784030","data":{"timestamp":" 946869784030"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869791923","data":{"timestamp":" 946869791922"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.rand","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869801667","data":{"timestamp":" 946869801666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869809228","data":{"timestamp":" 946869809227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8a108d1d-3688-449a-b7ab-0a4ea152923b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869819095","data":{"timestamp":" 946869819095"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869819996","data":{"timestamp":" 946869819996"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869820661","data":{"timestamp":" 946869820661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869821290","data":{"timestamp":" 946869821289"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869821510","data":{"timestamp":" 946869821509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869822266","data":{"timestamp":" 946869822266"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869825292","data":{"timestamp":" 946869825292"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869826589","data":{"timestamp":" 946869826588"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALIMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869827188","data":{"timestamp":" 946869827188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" CHINTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869827957","data":{"timestamp":" 946869827956"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869828035","data":{"timestamp":" 946869828035"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869829044","data":{"timestamp":" 946869829041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869831533","data":{"timestamp":" 946869831532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869833307","data":{"timestamp":" 946869833307"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALININUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALININUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869834045","data":{"timestamp":" 946869834044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869834295","data":{"timestamp":" 946869834295"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869834798","data":{"timestamp":" 946869834798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869834886","data":{"timestamp":" 946869834885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869836001","data":{"timestamp":" 946869836000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869837553","data":{"timestamp":" 946869837552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" ILIYONG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869837578","data":{"timestamp":" 946869837578"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AA"," userResponse":" AA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869838099","data":{"timestamp":" 946869838098"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869840923","data":{"timestamp":" 946869840923"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869841997","data":{"timestamp":" 946869841996"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869842905","data":{"timestamp":" 946869842905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869846000","data":{"timestamp":" 946869846000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869846712","data":{"timestamp":" 946869846712"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869847306","data":{"timestamp":" 946869847306"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869848287","data":{"timestamp":" 946869848287"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869849294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869849294"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869850041","data":{"timestamp":" 946869850041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869850934","data":{"timestamp":" 946869850934"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869854267","data":{"timestamp":" 946869854265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869854930","data":{"timestamp":" 946869854929"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869855473","data":{"timestamp":" 946869855472"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869856092","data":{"timestamp":" 946869856092"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869859387","data":{"timestamp":" 946869859387"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869860250","data":{"timestamp":" 946869860249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869861460","data":{"timestamp":" 946869861460"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZUILIWA"," userResponse":" ILIZUILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869862379","data":{"timestamp":" 946869862379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869863214","data":{"timestamp":" 946869863214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869863343","data":{"timestamp":" 946869863343"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869863825","data":{"timestamp":" 946869863825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869864047","data":{"timestamp":" 946869864047"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869864699","data":{"timestamp":" 946869864699"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869867390","data":{"timestamp":" 946869867389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIA"," userResponse":" NILILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869868865","data":{"timestamp":" 946869868864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869870983","data":{"timestamp":" 946869870981"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869871831","data":{"timestamp":" 946869871830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKULA"," userResponse":" SIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869872546","data":{"timestamp":" 946869872546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869873152","data":{"timestamp":" 946869873152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869873432","data":{"timestamp":" 946869873432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869874295","data":{"timestamp":" 946869874295"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869877308","data":{"timestamp":" 946869877308"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869878503","data":{"timestamp":" 946869878502"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869878823","data":{"timestamp":" 946869878823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869879773","data":{"timestamp":" 946869879773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869881075","data":{"timestamp":" 946869881074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" ULITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869884564","data":{"timestamp":" 946869884563"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ULIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869885206","data":{"timestamp":" 946869885205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869885688","data":{"timestamp":" 946869885688"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869886174","data":{"timestamp":" 946869886173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869886677","data":{"timestamp":" 946869886677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869887129","data":{"timestamp":" 946869887128"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869887385","data":{"timestamp":" 946869887384"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869888018","data":{"timestamp":" 946869888017"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869891067","data":{"timestamp":" 946869891066"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869892061","data":{"timestamp":" 946869892060"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869892950","data":{"timestamp":" 946869892950"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIVAA"," userResponse":" KUIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869893593","data":{"timestamp":" 946869893593"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869894191","data":{"timestamp":" 946869894191"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869897764","data":{"timestamp":" 946869897762"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ULITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869898129","data":{"timestamp":" 946869898128"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869899332","data":{"timestamp":" 946869899331"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869902081","data":{"timestamp":" 946869902081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869902314","data":{"timestamp":" 946869902314"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869902974","data":{"timestamp":" 946869902972"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUDI"," userResponse":" BUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869903420","data":{"timestamp":" 946869903419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869904885","data":{"timestamp":" 946869904885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTABASAMU"," userResponse":" KUTABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869905642","data":{"timestamp":" 946869905641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869908769","data":{"timestamp":" 946869908769"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869908960","data":{"timestamp":" 946869908960"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869909617","data":{"timestamp":" 946869909617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869910227","data":{"timestamp":" 946869910227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869910824","data":{"timestamp":" 946869910823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869912181","data":{"timestamp":" 946869912181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869913380","data":{"timestamp":" 946869913380"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869914274","data":{"timestamp":" 946869914273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIPA"," userResponse":" ALINIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869914989","data":{"timestamp":" 946869914989"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869915791","data":{"timestamp":" 946869915791"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869917222","data":{"timestamp":" 946869917221"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDI"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869918241","data":{"timestamp":" 946869918241"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" ILIYONG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869918272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869918272"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARA"," userResponse":" ARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869919019","data":{"timestamp":" 946869919018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANO"," userResponse":" MANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869921381","data":{"timestamp":" 946869921381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869922567","data":{"timestamp":" 946869922567"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIITUMA"," userResponse":" ULIITUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869923693","data":{"timestamp":" 946869923693"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869924426","data":{"timestamp":" 946869924425"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi uliituma mama alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869927692","data":{"timestamp":" 946869927691"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869928296","data":{"timestamp":" 946869928296"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869929206","data":{"timestamp":" 946869929204"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869930167","data":{"timestamp":" 946869930167"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869930380","data":{"timestamp":" 946869930379"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869931190","data":{"timestamp":" 946869931189"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869932288","data":{"timestamp":" 946869932287"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVAA"," userResponse":" TULIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869932877","data":{"timestamp":" 946869932877"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869933572","data":{"timestamp":" 946869933571"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869934494","data":{"timestamp":" 946869934493"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869936327","data":{"timestamp":" 946869936326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku huo sote mimi na mwezi tulivaa kofia zetu kisha tukatabasamu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATABASAMU"," userResponse":" TUKATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869939490","data":{"timestamp":" 946869939489"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFURAHI"," userResponse":" TULIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869940198","data":{"timestamp":" 946869940198"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869943620","data":{"timestamp":" 946869943620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNADHANI"," userResponse":" UNADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869944145","data":{"timestamp":" 946869944145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869945408","data":{"timestamp":" 946869945407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAHITAJI"," userResponse":" LINAHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869946198","data":{"timestamp":" 946869946197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unadhani jua linahitaji kofia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869949422","data":{"timestamp":" 946869949422"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIA"," userResponse":" KISIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869949641","data":{"timestamp":" 946869949641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869950240","data":{"timestamp":" 946869950240"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869950980","data":{"timestamp":" 946869950979"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869951894","data":{"timestamp":" 946869951893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869952763","data":{"timestamp":" 946869952763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEVAA"," userResponse":" NIMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869953280","data":{"timestamp":" 946869953279"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869955979","data":{"timestamp":" 946869955977"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869956058","data":{"timestamp":" 946869956058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 6e988d22-6a1f-45e1-94c1-84296bee6f03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisia ni kofia gani ambayo nimevaa leo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870063754","data":{"timestamp":" 946870063753"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 1c743d73-0a23-493c-acd5-debdac233f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870075441","data":{"timestamp":" 946870075441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 1c743d73-0a23-493c-acd5-debdac233f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870075548","data":{"timestamp":" 946870075548"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 1c743d73-0a23-493c-acd5-debdac233f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870091220","data":{"timestamp":" 946870091220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 1c743d73-0a23-493c-acd5-debdac233f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870110005","data":{"timestamp":" 946870110004"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 1c743d73-0a23-493c-acd5-debdac233f3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870124737","data":{"timestamp":" 946870124736"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870124979","data":{"timestamp":" 946870124978"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870125435","data":{"timestamp":" 946870125434"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870125886","data":{"timestamp":" 946870125885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870126213","data":{"timestamp":" 946870126211"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870127023","data":{"timestamp":" 946870127022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870127621","data":{"timestamp":" 946870127620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870127865","data":{"timestamp":" 946870127864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870128649","data":{"timestamp":" 946870128649"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870131377","data":{"timestamp":" 946870131376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870132350","data":{"timestamp":" 946870132350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870132788","data":{"timestamp":" 946870132788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870132978","data":{"timestamp":" 946870132978"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870133579","data":{"timestamp":" 946870133579"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870136685","data":{"timestamp":" 946870136685"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870137332","data":{"timestamp":" 946870137331"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870138100","data":{"timestamp":" 946870138100"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870141166","data":{"timestamp":" 946870141166"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870141834","data":{"timestamp":" 946870141834"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870142687","data":{"timestamp":" 946870142686"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870142910","data":{"timestamp":" 946870142910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870143663","data":{"timestamp":" 946870143663"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870144517","data":{"timestamp":" 946870144517"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870145617","data":{"timestamp":" 946870145616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870146642","data":{"timestamp":" 946870146642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870147557","data":{"timestamp":" 946870147557"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870148642","data":{"timestamp":" 946870148641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870149069","data":{"timestamp":" 946870149068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870149692","data":{"timestamp":" 946870149691"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870149878","data":{"timestamp":" 946870149878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870150479","data":{"timestamp":" 946870150478"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870153731","data":{"timestamp":" 946870153730"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870154893","data":{"timestamp":" 946870154893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870155616","data":{"timestamp":" 946870155616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870159094","data":{"timestamp":" 946870159093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870159726","data":{"timestamp":" 946870159726"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870160158","data":{"timestamp":" 946870160157"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870160678","data":{"timestamp":" 946870160677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870161178","data":{"timestamp":" 946870161178"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870161398","data":{"timestamp":" 946870161398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870162100","data":{"timestamp":" 946870162099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870164976","data":{"timestamp":" 946870164975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870165565","data":{"timestamp":" 946870165565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870166098","data":{"timestamp":" 946870166097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870166571","data":{"timestamp":" 946870166570"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870169703","data":{"timestamp":" 946870169702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870170467","data":{"timestamp":" 946870170467"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870171417","data":{"timestamp":" 946870171416"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870172775","data":{"timestamp":" 946870172774"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870173447","data":{"timestamp":" 946870173446"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870173821","data":{"timestamp":" 946870173821"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870174355","data":{"timestamp":" 946870174354"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870175437","data":{"timestamp":" 946870175436"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870176552","data":{"timestamp":" 946870176552"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUAMSHA"," userResponse":" KUMUAMSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870179732","data":{"timestamp":" 946870179732"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870179947","data":{"timestamp":" 946870179947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870180337","data":{"timestamp":" 946870180337"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870180846","data":{"timestamp":" 946870180846"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870182053","data":{"timestamp":" 946870182052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870182925","data":{"timestamp":" 946870182924"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870183976","data":{"timestamp":" 946870183975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870184628","data":{"timestamp":" 946870184628"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870184893","data":{"timestamp":" 946870184893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870185480","data":{"timestamp":" 946870185480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walitembea kwenda katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870188793","data":{"timestamp":" 946870188792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870189156","data":{"timestamp":" 946870189155"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870189625","data":{"timestamp":" 946870189624"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870190197","data":{"timestamp":" 946870190197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870190395","data":{"timestamp":" 946870190395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870190994","data":{"timestamp":" 946870190994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walisubiri ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870193405","data":{"timestamp":" 946870193404"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870193861","data":{"timestamp":" 946870193861"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870195078","data":{"timestamp":" 946870195077"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikufika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUFIKA"," userResponse":" HAIKUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870198124","data":{"timestamp":" 946870198124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870198799","data":{"timestamp":" 946870198798"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870199616","data":{"timestamp":" 946870199615"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870200083","data":{"timestamp":" 946870200082"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870200535","data":{"timestamp":" 946870200533"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870201041","data":{"timestamp":" 946870201040"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walifika pale kwenye kituo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870204576","data":{"timestamp":" 946870204576"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALILALAMIKA"," userResponse":" WALILALAMIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870205099","data":{"timestamp":" 946870205099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870205701","data":{"timestamp":" 946870205701"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870206786","data":{"timestamp":" 946870206786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walilalamika kwani basi ilichelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHELEWA"," userResponse":" ILICHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870209216","data":{"timestamp":" 946870209215"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870210523","data":{"timestamp":" 946870210522"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi imetuacha?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMETUACHA"," userResponse":" IMETUACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870213496","data":{"timestamp":" 946870213495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870214585","data":{"timestamp":" 946870214584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870214866","data":{"timestamp":" 946870214866"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870216131","data":{"timestamp":" 946870216130"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa na wasiwasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870219304","data":{"timestamp":" 946870219303"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTAWEZA"," userResponse":" HATUTAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870219936","data":{"timestamp":" 946870219935"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870220884","data":{"timestamp":" 946870220883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutaweza kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870223755","data":{"timestamp":" 946870223755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITAPATA"," userResponse":" SITAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870224093","data":{"timestamp":" 946870224093"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870224641","data":{"timestamp":" 946870224641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870224726","data":{"timestamp":" 946870224726"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870225408","data":{"timestamp":" 946870225408"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870226684","data":{"timestamp":" 946870226683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sitapata sare yangu ya shule aliwaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870230402","data":{"timestamp":" 946870230402"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870230540","data":{"timestamp":" 946870230540"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870231100","data":{"timestamp":" 946870231099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870232071","data":{"timestamp":" 946870232071"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATA"," userResponse":" WALIKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870232878","data":{"timestamp":" 946870232878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870233680","data":{"timestamp":" 946870233680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKARUDI"," userResponse":" WAKARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870234538","data":{"timestamp":" 946870234538"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watu walikata tamaa wakarudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870237286","data":{"timestamp":" 946870237286"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870237912","data":{"timestamp":" 946870237912"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870238886","data":{"timestamp":" 946870238886"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870240390","data":{"timestamp":" 946870240389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKATAA"," userResponse":" AKAKATAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870241146","data":{"timestamp":" 946870241146"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Ebei alilia akakataa kwenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870243489","data":{"timestamp":" 946870243487"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870244030","data":{"timestamp":" 946870244029"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870245525","data":{"timestamp":" 946870245525"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMTULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870247167","data":{"timestamp":" 946870247167"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUTASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870248207","data":{"timestamp":" 946870248206"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yake alimtuliza Tutasubiri zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870251668","data":{"timestamp":" 946870251667"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870253070","data":{"timestamp":" 946870253070"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISIKIA"," userResponse":" WALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870253906","data":{"timestamp":" 946870253905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla walisikia kelele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870256616","data":{"timestamp":" 946870256616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAONA"," userResponse":" WAKAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870257232","data":{"timestamp":" 946870257231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VUMBI"," userResponse":" VUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870257991","data":{"timestamp":" 946870257991"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaona vumbi hewani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEWANI"," userResponse":" HEWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870260438","data":{"timestamp":" 946870260438"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870261080","data":{"timestamp":" 946870261080"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870261943","data":{"timestamp":" 946870261943"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ilikuwa inakuja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870265373","data":{"timestamp":" 946870265373"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870265874","data":{"timestamp":" 946870265873"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870266536","data":{"timestamp":" 946870266535"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870266974","data":{"timestamp":" 946870266973"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini basi haikuwa buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870270102","data":{"timestamp":" 946870270101"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870270753","data":{"timestamp":" 946870270752"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haikuwa kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870273231","data":{"timestamp":" 946870273231"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870273664","data":{"timestamp":" 946870273664"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870274449","data":{"timestamp":" 946870274449"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870275399","data":{"timestamp":" 946870275399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870275807","data":{"timestamp":" 946870275807"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870276486","data":{"timestamp":" 946870276486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi ile ilikuwa nyekundu na ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870280044","data":{"timestamp":" 946870280044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" WALIOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870282363","data":{"timestamp":" 946870282363"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliosubiri waliiangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WALIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870285749","data":{"timestamp":" 946870285749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUINGIA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870286292","data":{"timestamp":" 946870286291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakuingia ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870289581","data":{"timestamp":" 946870289581"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870290563","data":{"timestamp":" 946870290562"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva aliita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" ALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870293689","data":{"timestamp":" 946870293689"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" TUMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870294153","data":{"timestamp":" 946870294152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870295021","data":{"timestamp":" 946870295020"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870296011","data":{"timestamp":" 946870296010"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tumechelewa sana leo alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870299466","data":{"timestamp":" 946870299465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870299631","data":{"timestamp":" 946870299631"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870300023","data":{"timestamp":" 946870300022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870300526","data":{"timestamp":" 946870300526"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870301227","data":{"timestamp":" 946870301227"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870301411","data":{"timestamp":" 946870301411"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870301922","data":{"timestamp":" 946870301922"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870302670","data":{"timestamp":" 946870302670"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei na mama yake walikuwa wa kwanza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870305156","data":{"timestamp":" 946870305156"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870305645","data":{"timestamp":" 946870305645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870306361","data":{"timestamp":" 946870306361"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870307347","data":{"timestamp":" 946870307346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870307916","data":{"timestamp":" 946870307916"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870307983","data":{"timestamp":" 946870307983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870308572","data":{"timestamp":" 946870308572"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870308917","data":{"timestamp":" 946870308916"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870309395","data":{"timestamp":" 946870309395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870310148","data":{"timestamp":" 946870310148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara kila mmoja aliingia ndani ya basi ile ndogo nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870313389","data":{"timestamp":" 946870313389"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870314201","data":{"timestamp":" 946870314201"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870315402","data":{"timestamp":" 946870315401"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei aliangalia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870318201","data":{"timestamp":" 946870318200"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870318663","data":{"timestamp":" 946870318662"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870319344","data":{"timestamp":" 946870319344"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870320049","data":{"timestamp":" 946870320048"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870320900","data":{"timestamp":" 946870320899"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870321469","data":{"timestamp":" 946870321469"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870321643","data":{"timestamp":" 946870321642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870322243","data":{"timestamp":" 946870322243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona watu wengi zaidi katika kituo cha basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870325307","data":{"timestamp":" 946870325306"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870325891","data":{"timestamp":" 946870325890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870326647","data":{"timestamp":" 946870326646"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870328070","data":{"timestamp":" 946870328069"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" WALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870329158","data":{"timestamp":" 946870329158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIFIKIA"," userResponse":" KUIFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870329858","data":{"timestamp":" 946870329858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata wengine zaidi walikimbia kuifikia basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870332469","data":{"timestamp":" 946870332469"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870333350","data":{"timestamp":" 946870333350"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870334413","data":{"timestamp":" 946870334413"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikuwa wamechelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHELEWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHELEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870336997","data":{"timestamp":" 946870336996"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870338064","data":{"timestamp":" 946870338064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ILIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870338595","data":{"timestamp":" 946870338594"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870339498","data":{"timestamp":" 946870339497"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi iliondoka kwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870342557","data":{"timestamp":" 946870342556"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870343023","data":{"timestamp":" 946870343022"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870343559","data":{"timestamp":" 946870343559"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870343823","data":{"timestamp":" 946870343823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870344763","data":{"timestamp":" 946870344763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wapi basi kubwa ya buluu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870347119","data":{"timestamp":" 946870347118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870347580","data":{"timestamp":" 946870347580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870348220","data":{"timestamp":" 946870348220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870349098","data":{"timestamp":" 946870349097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama yake Ebei aliuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870352486","data":{"timestamp":" 946870352486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIHARIBIKA"," userResponse":" ILIHARIBIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870353278","data":{"timestamp":" 946870353275"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870354361","data":{"timestamp":" 946870354360"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliharibika dereva alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870356990","data":{"timestamp":" 946870356990"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870357985","data":{"timestamp":" 946870357985"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ITAKUJA"," userResponse":" ITAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870359245","data":{"timestamp":" 946870359243"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kesho itakuja aliongeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONGEZA"," userResponse":" ALIONGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870362291","data":{"timestamp":" 946870362291"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870363369","data":{"timestamp":" 946870363369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870363833","data":{"timestamp":" 946870363832"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870363957","data":{"timestamp":" 946870363957"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870364760","data":{"timestamp":" 946870364760"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei hakujali rangi ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870367587","data":{"timestamp":" 946870367587"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUJALI"," userResponse":" HAKUJALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870368323","data":{"timestamp":" 946870368323"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUBWA"," userResponse":" UKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870368510","data":{"timestamp":" 946870368510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870369284","data":{"timestamp":" 946870369284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakujali ukubwa wa basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870373097","data":{"timestamp":" 946870373097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870373821","data":{"timestamp":" 946870373821"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870374339","data":{"timestamp":" 946870374338"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870375021","data":{"timestamp":" 946870375021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870375896","data":{"timestamp":" 946870375896"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870376626","data":{"timestamp":" 946870376625"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKWENDA"," userResponse":" INAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870377478","data":{"timestamp":" 946870377478"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870380103","data":{"timestamp":" 946870380102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870380192","data":{"timestamp":" 946870380192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870387441","data":{"timestamp":" 946870387441"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870394794","data":{"timestamp":" 946870394794"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870403832","data":{"timestamp":" 946870403830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870525904","data":{"timestamp":" 946870525902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 2e346b29-949c-496a-b55e-1b49be496979"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alifurahi kuwa basi hii ilikuwa inakwenda mjini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870526097","data":{"timestamp":" 946870526097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bf79b03a-73a6-41fb-a8ec-687cce51a1f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.6__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870537661","data":{"timestamp":" 946870537660"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" bf79b03a-73a6-41fb-a8ec-687cce51a1f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870548887","data":{"timestamp":" 946870548887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870549395","data":{"timestamp":" 946870549395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870550188","data":{"timestamp":" 946870550188"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870553035","data":{"timestamp":" 946870553034"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870553595","data":{"timestamp":" 946870553595"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870554358","data":{"timestamp":" 946870554357"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870557344","data":{"timestamp":" 946870557343"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870557935","data":{"timestamp":" 946870557935"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870558715","data":{"timestamp":" 946870558715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870561882","data":{"timestamp":" 946870561882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870562139","data":{"timestamp":" 946870562138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870562853","data":{"timestamp":" 946870562852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sifuri ni bila."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870565738","data":{"timestamp":" 946870565738"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870566253","data":{"timestamp":" 946870566252"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870567057","data":{"timestamp":" 946870567056"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja mbili tatu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870569939","data":{"timestamp":" 946870569938"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870570499","data":{"timestamp":" 946870570499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870571266","data":{"timestamp":" 946870571265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nne tano sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870574220","data":{"timestamp":" 946870574220"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870574792","data":{"timestamp":" 946870574792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870575581","data":{"timestamp":" 946870575580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Saba nane tisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870578438","data":{"timestamp":" 946870578437"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870578707","data":{"timestamp":" 946870578706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870579497","data":{"timestamp":" 946870579497"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870582783","data":{"timestamp":" 946870582781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870582871","data":{"timestamp":" 946870582870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873273117","data":{"timestamp":" 946873273117"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873391885","data":{"timestamp":" 946873391884"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 5d961526-61a1-4bc6-b91d-af2c2bc9bc3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__numbers_counting_song__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kumi ni vidole!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946873391989","data":{"timestamp":" 946873391989"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000103_055838"," gameId":" 8638ce67-978f-4e72-9c8b-2fd1a81295ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}